

Contact

+48 796 360 728

kwapiszr@gmail.com

Marii Dąbrowskiej 15D

Abilities

- high work ethic
- communication
- cooperation
- independence in making decisions
- stress resistance
- very good work organization

Hobbies

- automotive
- cooking
- front-end coding
- sport
- artificial intelligence

RAFAŁ KWAPISZ

abaut me

I am 29 years old and from the beginning of my career I was driven by the desire to develop professionally in the catering industry. After quite a long adventure, it was time for a change. I would like to develop further by changing the environment and the profession itself.

experience

chef

Yana Sushi

2021-2023

- Group management of up to 5 people.
- Inventory management monitoring and controlling ingredient inventories, ordering deliveries, ensuring proper storage and consumption of products.
- Tool and equipment management ensuring kitchen equipment is in good condition and carrying out maintenance.
- Direct contact with representatives of catering companies and negotiations of attractive prices.

chef

Mahō Sushi

2019-2021

- Team management recruitment, training, motivating and supervising kitchen staff.
- Problem solving dealing with crisis situations such as breakdowns of kitchen equipment or conflicts within the team.
- Menu planning creating menus, selecting dishes and ingredients, taking into account seasonality and customer preferences.

Education

Zespół Szkół Ekonomicznych nr 1 w Krakowie

Hotelier major 2010-2014